i just started this 10 minute timer and when it hits zero that room all the way over there full
of money will explode and the only man that can stop it is this man in this straight jacket this
video is completely real time you'll know this is exactly 10 minutes long there are no cuts you see
everything and if darcy does not escape his jacket and get through all five floors of this tower and
press that button before the timer hits zero his money explodes all right he's coming down
okay this is our first ever real-time shoot i gotta go quick i gotta go go go go hey
Hey, hurry, unhatch this.
Wait, how did he get out of that jacket so fast?
It doesn't matter.
This next floor is twice as hard to escape.
All right, lower, slower, slower.
Holy.
You put fire in there?
Okay, so to get out of the metal cage,
you need to use the lock pick on the floor.
Hurry up!
Faster!
Darcy!
Come on!
Oh, my gosh.
Even with a tool, picking a lock takes some fidgeting.
He has to perfectly align all three pins inside the lock
in order to break free.
By the way, in order to prove this video is 100% real-time,
Starting now, you're going to see an unbroken shot of Darcy
in the corner of the full video.
And as of now.
A minute has gone by, and he's still in the first room.
And remember, he still needs to get through all five
floors of this tower and press the button in time.
The button's right here.
To keep his quarter of a million dollars from exploding, Matt.
I'm getting so much anxiety.
Please go faster.
Wait, Matt, he's breaking the law.
Is he making good time or not?
All right, so now, yeah.
But he's about to go down to an even more difficult room.
Be careful.
Don't catch on fire.
Darcy, go.
Come on, what are you doing?
Go, go.
He's coming down the road. He's in the glue room now. Welcome to floor number four
He's already made it through room four. This is floor number four. Okay, so this entire floor is now covered in glue
He has to choose between monkey bar or walking across the glue and I would very much advise
He does not walk across the glue. So far so good on the monkey bars. Keep going buddy. Come on!
Two minutes has gone by!
What's going on in your head man?
Oh, no.
What do I do?
Why are you spinning?
Stop spinning.
If he falls, that is not good, because that is the stickiest glue in the world.
I'm not even joking.
He'll lose his shoes.
Oh, yeah.
It's already been two minutes.
Dude, he's swinging.
He didn't touch the ground once.
Man is glue-less.
He made it to the exit.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
He's about to lift up that lid, and now he's about to enter the craziest room.
Keep taking us down.
Watch this.
You're going to see him jump down.
Oh, my god, boys.
I'm so tired.
All right.
All right, Darcy's struggling, but he's making his way down
the ropes of floor three, the boulder room.
This one should be relatively simple.
All right, Darcy, see that giant boulder?
Yes.
Well, these two ropes are the only thing preventing it
from barreling down this ramp.
Darcy, there's a machete.
You needed to get out of this room.
Yes.
Darcy, you're losing time.
What do you think you'd do with the knife?
Got to cut these ropes.
Cut that rope.
You're running out of time.
Normally in our videos, when someone does something
this slow, like we cut it out.
But this is live.
We literally can't cut it out.
I am freaking out seven minutes remain and he's almost done with one of two ropes
There's like some James Bond stuff right here as he goes lower the floors are gonna get harder and take longer
He's actually not making as good pace as you would want him to make that robe is gonna take him the longest because of how
Thick it is. Oh cut the rope. He's wasting a lot of time. Dude. He's behind right now. This knife is so dull
You're gonna have to hurry under seven minutes remain before your two hundred fifty thousand dollars explode
Jimmy I'm going to die from old age before he finishes cutting this rope
Oh
When he cuts that second rope, it's something crazy gonna happen and Darcy
All right, I guess Darcy's locked in Jimmy what is gonna happen when he cuts the rope
Well, this boulder is gonna go through the window. Tell me please all you need to do
Yes, hold on to that when he cuts the rope. Okay, that's that's I can handle that. There's no way I'm losing
There's 250 grand because of this stupid rope Jimmy. Why'd you find the slowest man possible at cutting a rope Darcy?
Jose, hurry up.
Like I told you at the start, this is real time.
You're seeing everything.
Obviously, Darcy is pretty occupied right now.
But if he could talk to us, he'd probably
tell us about the fact that he is a world-class escape artist.
And apparently, that doesn't translate over to cutting ropes.
Darcy, you spent a whole minute on this.
He only has six minutes left.
Oh, my god.
Cut faster.
Come on.
Bro, you have got to cut the rope a lot faster.
My gosh.
Oh, he's about to finish the last rope.
Darcy, push the boulder down the ramp.
So the boulder's just going to?
You'll see in a bit.
Okay, he's pushing the boulder now.
Brace yourself!
Back up!
Darcy, quick, I want you to grab the rope from the ceiling
and attach it to your pants.
And please make sure it is 100% connected, okay?
All right.
What is he gonna do?
Okay, Darcy, now step down, go to the edge,
and turn around.
Watch this.
Watch what?
Go to the green arrow, go to your right.
Here we go.
Oh my God, is he about to jump, bro?
Go to your right, go to your right.
What is he gonna do?
What is he doing?
All right, he's about to jump.
All right, Darcy, now you need to jump.
Oh my God, how am I supposed to do this?
Go, Darcy!
Darcy, jump!
What?
OK.
He has exactly five minutes left.
Stop the crane.
I don't know.
The crane operator's drunk.
You got to make it through the lasers.
This floor is by far the hardest yet.
Not only does he need to make it through this laser maze,
but if he accidentally touches a laser,
his money will instantly explode.
How am I going to do this?
There's so many lasers.
While he's doing this laser room,
I'm going to tell you guys about T-Mobile,
my new wireless partner.
Let's go here.
Mac.
What?
You probably know T-Mobile from this coverage map.
Yes, I do.
I do know that.
But here's the thing. Okay. You know great coverage is to be expected. Okay, but what T-Mobile has that other carriers don't
Jimmy look he's halfway through the lasers. Oh, he's on our side. Uh, but what makes T-Mobile special is they have something called magenta status
Okay, what is magenta status? It's where they treat you like a VIP. Okay
By just by using T-Mobile you can get reduced cost of hotel rooms
You can get free in-flight Wi-Fi access to VIP lounges. Go go go!
Oh, T-Bubble, T-Bubble, I'm stressing out.
Sorry if I'm forgetting lines.
And a bunch of other stuff.
And the best part is back.
It's right there.
Hey, let me finish the T-Bubble app.
Okay.
And the best part is, it's all,
Dean, jump in the water.
It's all available day one when you switch to T-Bubble.
So if you're not currently using T-Bubble,
start using now.
You can get all these perks literally today.
I need to catch my breath here.
Check it out for yourself.
Go to T-Mobile.com slash.
Oh, he's in the water.
Oh my God.
All right, this is it.
The last level.
He now has to open the four valves
in each corner of the room, allowing all the water to drain.
Then he can escape out the front door
and hit the button to save his money from blowing up.
You gotta turn these!
Turn these things!
Turn!
Turn the knob!
What's he doing?
I actually don't help him.
Well, let's see if he's smart enough to win the money.
Will he be able to hold his breath long enough
to unscrew all four valves?
Or will he run out of time?
While this guy is doing this intense challenge,
I want to tell you about the greatest tasting
chocolate on the planet, Feastables.
Matt!
What do you think of Feastables?
Oh, it's my favorite.
Oh, no, he's going for the one he finished.
Hey, hey, no, no, hey, do the other one, do the other one.
You've got to keep, how much time is left?
Oh, three minutes.
Oh, oh, yeah, he actually kind of just
wasted like 30 seconds.
He can do this if he just hurries up.
Come on, catch your breath, let's go.
Mac, he's about to go under, go around the side,
see if it opens.
All right, keep turning.
Oh, he did it, other side, other side.
Two to go, baby!
Alright, he's now making his way to the other side.
You gotta go swim down!
This is coming down to the wire.
I cannot imagine how absolutely
exhausted he must be.
Alright, so
he has two minutes and ten seconds
to, right over here, press that red button
or his money will explode. It's coming down to the wire.
You got it! You got it!
Don't know what to do. Normally we do cunts
and edits, but this is like real time.
Everything I'm saying is making it
He's getting close he's getting close
He just did it. You got out for he did it. All right the final door a minute 50 seconds
I went out. I know yes open this door run and press the button. How much time is yeah, just under two minutes
How was he gonna pull this off? I don't get it. You're gonna get what if you stand there you might want to back up
Why it still needs to train fast back in case he failed that bomb will blow up
So I need you to just like hide behind the sandbags over there if he messes up. Okay? Okay, just trust me
You have to unscrew all the latches
Get him out of there! Come on!
Almost a minute! Come on! Come on!
Bro, I don't know if he's gonna make it at this point. The door is stuck because there's too much water pressure
He needs to wait for it to drain more
Wait, Jimmy the water's starting to come out the front door! Turn it! Turn it!
Pull it! You gotta go, buddy! You have got to go!
He's stuck in that one.
He can't get it.
He can't figure out how to open a door.
Oh, he literally had 45 seconds to hit this button.
Hey!
Bro!
You gotta slide through that door!
We won with 19 seconds left.
We cleared the money out of the way of the bomb,
and asked what he was going to spend it on.
I'm having a baby tomorrow.
What?
And then we blew the building up.
I hope you enjoyed the explosion.
We have to make this video exactly 10 minutes.